Anthony Perez

□ antrp93@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/antrp93

+1 806-781-0434

8

github.com/antrp93LCA

Summary

I've always been fascinated with technology and have always asked questions to better understand the technology I surround myself with everyday. Which is why I am currently pursuing a Full-Stack certificate at Lubbock Coding Academy.

I've traveled as a roadie and set up live performances with audio and lighting. Helped build a few stages, most notably, I helped with the MTV Woodie Awards. I did a stint in Tejano gigs for a company called Pantera Staging Company as well.

I've been in the Cinema industry as a Projectionist for 3 years currently. I mostly work with digital cinema but have had the privilege to handle both 35mm and 70mm projection. Worked heavily with reel to reel projection but have been getting more into 70mm platter projection.

Recently, I have had the pleasure to get hands on experience within the .NET framework, this includes learning and creating applications with HTML/CSS/C#/MySQL/Typescript and GIT.

My Capstone project is building a web application that focuses on creating the *conscious consumer* by providing detailed information about certain food products that they buy. Users will be able to view a specific product's nutritional facts, dietary factors, allergen information, and specific lifestyle details as well. Right now the primary focus is food products, but will look to expand to other products such as automobiles, cosmetic, and technology products as well.

Experience



Coding Instructor

Nov 2019- Present

Lubbock Coding Academy

- I help current students (Intro To Web & C# classes) at Lubbock Coding Academy with their coursework by
 providing in-class tutoring. As well as scheduling tutoring sessions with classmates to help them understand
 the curriculum outside of the classroom. I meet with individual students on designated days throughout the
 week and I hold a group tutoring session every Sunday.
- I also take this skill set and help with LCA's Early Code program, where we teach middle-schoolers HTML &
 CSS and apply the technical skillset to build a business website of their choice.



70mm Projectionist

Aug 2019- Present

Science Spectrum

- Operate Imax Projection machinery to show educational movies according to the schedule.
- Keep track of multiple data-sets to ensure that everything in the Projection booth is fully operational.
- A level of care goes into preserving and maintaining the 70mm film that we handle on a daily basis and I am responsible for ensuring that the quality of each show is not tarnished by malpractice.



Projectionist Aug 2016- Present

Triple Tap Ventures LLC (Alamo Drafthouse Cinema)

- Build shows digitally through a computer terminal using Sony's Theater Management System. Manage shows through the same interface as schedule changes weekly.
- Run specialty screenings by quality checking and testing live theater equipment such as PA speaker, microphones, spotlights, laptop etc. This also requires knowing the interface of the Sony 320 & 515 digital projectors.
- Occasionally, we do run 35mm film events, which includes inspecting and threading the print with care.
- We serve as a in-house IT for the venue by diagnosing potential issues with equipment and communicating with specialists in assisting with fixing any higher level technical issues.
- Keep a line of communication with multiple departments of the company to ensure that every show will run
 when scheduled. This involves checking with our booker or distributors to double check that any cinema
 drives are ordered and are headed to the venue in a timely fashion. Even coordinating with creative teams
 to ensure that anything to be presented in the theater meets a certain level of quality.

Education



Austin Coding Academy

2019 - 2020

Full Stack Certification, Web Development



Coronado High School

2009 - 2012

Skills



35mm Projection • 70mm Projection • HTML • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • C# • SQL • ASP.NET MVC • .NET Framework • Entity Framework (EF) Core